koken.me 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy / Koken

Koken is committed to respecting and protecting your online privacy. We are providing this Privacy Policy for Koken (the "Software") and the [Koken Store](http://store.koken.me/ "Koken Store") so you may understand our policies with regard to your personal information.

## Gathering and Use of Information

Koken will only collect your personal information when the Software is installed, you voluntarily sign-up for our mailing list, or you create an account at the Koken Store. Information we collect from you will never be sold, rented or shared with third-parties.

## Information collected

Installations of the Software provide Koken with location information including the target server's Internet Protocol ("IP") address, domain name, date of installation, the Software version number, server PHP version, image processing library and email address should the administrator sign-up for our mailing list.

When Koken Store accounts are created we ask for your name and email address. Information regarding installations of the Software, including the target server's Internet Protocol ("IP") address and domain name, are automatically saved to your Koken Store account profile when an account is accessed through an installation of the Software. Deletion of installation data is available through your Koken Store account profile. 

You will have the option of saving your credit card data with your Koken Store account during the checkout process. We will encrypt your credit card and sensitive information at industry standards. This data will never be used or shared by Koken in any way without your permission. 

## Mailing Lists

If you sign up for our mailing list you may receive the occasional email newsletter from us. You may choose not to receive further emails by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email.

## Updates

Koken reserves the right to update this privacy policy at any time. Updates to our privacy policy will be sent to the email address you have provided us with.

Questions concerning this policy may be directed to [Koken support](http://help.koken.me/customer/portal/emails/new).

_Last modified: December 1, 2015_
